ケンリイ KEN KEONG LEE

PERSONAL STATEMENT

After 3 years in DRAM design, I am looking for new opportunity beyond DRAM design within the realm of semiconductor circuit design. I am intrigued with the advance design tools such as systhesis, APR, Pulsic, Analog floor planing, etc. as DRAM design does not involve the use of advance EDAs. Throughout the last 3 years in DRAM design, I was trained in various design task from design row circuitry, spice verification, analog design and layout. Through various projects, I was trained in different part of the design flow from schematics to Tapeout. During downtime between projects, I explored various open source circuit design projects such as Skywater, Efabless, Opensource EDA tools which intrigue my interest in other aspect of circuit design in particular automated steps between netlist and layout procedures.

WORK EXPERIENCE

_		
Period	${\rm Aug} \; 2020 \; \sim \;$	
Employer	Zentel Japan ゼンテルジャパン 大阪	
Job Title	Senior Engineer 主任技師	
	JEDEC compliant DRAM, well versed in Spice verification logic and some analog circuits. Involved in at least ~ 4 project, including one custom DRAM project. Job scope involves from standard cells, circuit block design, making pre RC model schematics, post RC timing adjustment and RC analysis of simple analog circuits. In on project responsible for layout. DRAM testing theory, 1C1T row/column redundancy.	
Period Oct 2019 — March 2020		
Employer	Osaka University 大阪大学	
Job Title	Research Assistant	
	Neutrinoless double beta decay, cryogenic scintillating sensor, data analytic	
Period	July 2014 — Aug 2014 (Summer placement)	
Employer	Oxford Instrument Tubney Woods, Oxfordshire	
Job Title	SEPnet Student summer placement	
Mentor	MENTOR Daniel Strange, daniel.strange@oxinst.com	
	2 months internships, cryogenic superconducting magnet, problem solving	

Personal Skills

Language	English(native), Chinese(native), Malay(Fluent),
	Japanese(Business, JLPT N2), Cantonese(Conversational),
EDA DRAM	schematics-Virtuoso, layout-Jedat's ISMO, Calibre, spice-Finesim,
	pre/post RC spice, verilog pattern generation,
Semiconductor basic	transistors-Undergrad, Logics gates-Undergrad, circuit design-current job
Self Learn EDA	OpenROAD - synthesis, floorplan, APR (CTS, routing)
	Memory hierarchy, basic instruction set architecture
Programing	Python, C/C++, CAD, Labview, LaTeX, Git, Markdown
	Pytorch, FEA-ANSYS, KiCAD, ROOT, Geant4
Experiences	Dilution refrigerator, high pressure vacuum system

wire bonder, cumulative 3 months underground laboratory shift

EDUCATION

Period	September 2012 — July 2016	
Degree	MPhys	
University	University of Southampton	UK
Second Class Honour(Upper Division), £12 000 scholarship tuition fee		
	Graduation thesis: Flavour Composition and Energy Spectrum of A	Astro-
	physical Neutrino at IceCube	

Denzon	O + 1 0010 M 1 0000	
Period	October 2016 — March 2020	
Course	Experimental Physics*	
University	Osaka University	Japan
	*completion of studies with credits, 3 years 文部科学省: ship, 6 months research assistant	MEXT Scholar-
	Bolometer development for scintillating crystal at cryoger	ic temperature,
	Unsupervised learning for data analysis, dilution refrigera	
Period	January 2011 — June 2012	
LEVEL	Advance Level	
Institution	Tunku Abdul Rahman College(TARUC)	KL, Malaysia
	3A*1A, full tuition scholarship, pre-university/high schoo	l equivalent
Period	January 2006 — December 2010	
Level	SPM	
Institution	SMK Raja Abdullah	KL, Malaysia
	9A1B, O level equivalent	

Personal information

DOB 13/07/1993 Nationality Malaysian

Visa status 技術·人文知識·国際業務, PR pending(expected next year)

Linkedin uk.linkedin.com/pub/ken-keong-lee/9b/18b/885/

Personal Homepage hareyakana.github.io/cv/

Past Achievement

High Achiever Award 2012 by TARC

Full merit scholarship for A level studies at TARC

National Physics Quiz 2010 Bronze National Chemistry Quiz 2010 merit Level 2 Certificate in Book-keeping and Accounts 2010

Conferences/Articles/etc.

- Phys. Rev. D 103, 092008 CANDLES Collaboration "Low background measurement in CANDLES-III for studying the neutrino-less double beta decay of 48 Ca" co-authored
- International workshop on Revealing the history of the universe with underground particle and nuclear research 2019 Tohoku 2019 - "Development of Scintillating Bolometer for CANDLES" (Poster) co-authored
- JPS Autumn 2019 meeting "Bolometer Development using Neutron Transmutation Doped Ge in CANDLES for the study of Neutrinoless Double Beta decay" main presenter
- TAUP 2019 "Status of ⁴⁸Ca double beta decay search and its future prospect in CAN-DLES" co-presenter

Past research projects

Anomaly search through Unsupervised Machine Learning Phd Project Neutrinoless Double Beta Decay Phd Project Phd Project Low temperature Bolometer Development Dark Matter and IceCube experiment MPhys Project

Neutrino Oscillations Individual Dissertation

Plasmonics Individual Essay

VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCES

Period March 2010, April 2011

PLACE Ko Bulon and Satun in Thailand

English Camp for under privileged/abused children

PAST EXCHANGE INVOLVEMENT

Period 2009

PROGRAM Culture Exchange Program with Kumamoto Gakuen University Fuzoku

High School, Japan

Period 2010

PROGRAM Culture Exchange Program with Osaka Furitsu Minoh High School,

Japan